# Zakaria Wahyu Web Developer



ABOUT



Hallo, I'm Zakaria Wahyu Nur Utomo. I was born June 25th 1999 at Klaten, Central Java, Indonesia. As informatic engineering associate degree students of Telkom University, I have a lot of experience in web programming. I've good familiarity of PHP web framework like codeigniter and laravel. During my study, I was also appointed as a Project Manager for several project task. I'm creative person that like to create something new and able to solving some problem.



0

082 329 027 297



zakarianur6@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/zakariawahyu



www.zakariawahyu.site



github.com/zakariawahyu



Bandung, West Java, Indonesia

DACI	C SKI	110
DAJI	COVI	LLJ

HTML5	
CSS3	
MYSQL	
PHP	
CODEIGNITER	
LARAVEL	
JAVA	

# SOFTWARE SKILLS

PHOTOSHOP	
PREMIERE PRO	
ILLUSTRATOR	
ADOBE XD	
<b>UNITY 3D</b>	
ANDROID STUDIO	

## **EXPERIENCE**

## Web Developer Internship

2020

## Augmented Reality Enginer Internship

2019

## Web Programming Practicum Assistant

2018 - 2020

## Team Leader

2018 - 2019

#### **HUMAN RESOURCE TELKOM UNIVERSITY**

I'm became web developer to help Directorate of Human Resource Telkom University for developing staff structural position application so easier for HR to determine any vacant position. I use laravel framework to build this application.

#### PT. INOVASI SEMESTA ILMU

I had an opportunity to internship at PT. Inovasi Semesta Ilmu Bandung Company to build an application VR and AR based. The application used to promote tourism in Bandung more easier. I use Unity 3D to build this application and Samsung Gear 360 to take the VR.

#### **TELKOM APPLIED SCIENCES SCHOOL**

I'm an assistant practicum at many Telkom University Applied Sciences Schools study programs. I have a lot of experience for example help lecturers to practicum, recapitulation of values practicum, and create modules for practice html, css, php, Javascript and database every week for students.

#### PERFECTO 2.0

PERFECTO (PaMTKla Exhibition Roadshow and Fun Education Tryout) is a commite under the Directorate of Admission Telkom University which has a goals to hold roadshow activities and try out to promote and communicate about information of Telkom University to public.

## **EDUCATION**

## Telkom University

2017-2020

## Senior High School 1 Karanganom

2014-2017

#### **Associate Degree Of Informatic Engineering**

During 3 years of college I have a lot of experience in web programming, android programming, iot, and multimedia. But I am more focused to explore web programming

#### Natural Sciences

I was graduated at 2017. When I was SHS student, I had a lot of leadership experience because I joined National Flag Hoisting Troop

## CERTIFICATE

## Android Beginer

2020 - 2022

## Dicoding Indonesia

Learn basic android programming that learns how to create relative layouts, recycler view, activity and intent

## Android Expert

2020- 2022

## **Dicoding Indonesia**

Learn android fundamentals that learn how to make fragment, action bar, tab layout, navigation, services, broadcast receiver, alarm manager, job scheduler, viewmodel, widget, notification, firebase and webview